Dear,
you've finally arrived.
Sorry, Mr. Zhuang,
I'm late.
We finally meet.
You've been back for so long,
yet you never contacted me.
I thought you forgot your old friend.
Mr. Zhuang, you're too kind.
You've been following the news.
I've been too busy to get away.
You're starting to look like a real wife.
You're still way ahead of me.
Time doesn't fade a beauty.
You still have
a way with words.
What a coincidence.
Look,
someone you know is here too.
Jiang Li.
Mr. Zhou.
I thought you were in Fan State on a business trip.
Yeah.
But
the plan changed,
and I heard
Mr. Zhuang is here too,
so I came to visit.
Ms. Jiang,
we meet again.
Mr. Shen,
we really are fated to meet.
It turns out that
we are all acquaintances.
It seems that tonight
we really need to have a good drink.
Please.
Can Jiang Li really find out?
If she finds out,
how should I deal with that woman?
Honey,
I've been waiting for you in the bedroom for a long time.
I'll come in after I finish my work.
Okay?
Su...
Muchen.
Purple vine.
By the way,
when I accompanied the old man to France
to visit Charles,
I saw this girl's design draft,
and knew she was not an ordinary person.
Now she has become the chief designer of Golden Thread.
Your foresight
is indeed sharp.
Back then,
grandpa was against it,
but you
insisted on investing.
Now it seems
it was indeed a wise choice.
It's a pity
that Annie is too cautious.
I've tried to increase my shareholding many times,
but she always rejected it.
When the company goes public,
everyone here will have a chance to benefit.
The golden age of Golden Thread
has just begun.
Oh,
then at that time,
I will definitely increase my shareholding.
After all,
who wouldn't want to take a bite
of such tender lamb?
If that's the case,
why did you
reject the proposal
for limited release of Dark Fairy Tale?
After all,
I don't have a solid foundation
at Golden Thread.
I have to go with the majority.
Although I'm the biggest shareholder
besides the Lu family,
I only hold
10% of the shares.
Compared to the 80% held by the Lu family,
it's not worth mentioning.
What if
Mr. Zhou and I become your foundation?
Would you still go with the majority?
Jiang Li.
Leave it to me.
Oh?
Let's hear it.
The son-in-law of the Lu family,
and the future daughter-in-law.
We are both Lu family members
and not Lu family members.
If you can offer enough benefits,
we can provide equivalent chips.
What do you think
of this deal, Mr. Zhuang?
I was right about you.
Your words are bold.
Don't you think, Mr. Zhou?
Come on.
It hurts.
Are you crazy?
Saying those things to Zhuang Wan?
Do you like me?
I'm your brother-in-law.
You're Lu Xu's fiancée.
Let's stop here.
You lied to Lu Qianqian,
to Lu Xu,
and now you're lying to yourself.
Do you really love her?
Just like you did back then.
Did Lu Xu ask you to seduce me?
Yes.
He asked me to seduce you.
But so what?
Fate brought us together again.
Even if it's a bad relationship, it's still a relationship, isn't it?
Do you really love Lu Qianqian?
Or I'll put it another way.
If you and Lu Qianqian switch identities,
will you still love her?
If there were no Lu Xu,
and I met you again,
I would still do this.
Because we are both
weeds climbing up through thorns.
If there's a chance,
don't you want to
step on people like Lu Xu and Lu Qianqian?
I do.
So, are you willing to join me?
Aren't you afraid
I'm just using you?
I'll ask you one last time.
Do you like me?
Answer it.
Hello, Mr. Xu.
Zhou.
I heard you're in Binhai.
What a coincidence!
Mr. Guo, whom you've been trying to meet,
is with me right now.
I'll send you an address.
Come over quickly.
Mr. Xu,
it's too late today.
Maybe another day.
No,
Mr. Guo is leaving for the US tomorrow.
Dark Fairy Tale needs your overseas media resources.
It'll be hard to meet him
after he leaves.
I'm on my way.
Go.
Can you handle it alone?
You're here. How could you get lost?
Have some hot water.
Thanks.
Why are you in my room, Shen Jingmo?
Take a good look,
whose room is this?
Our Shen Family also owns properties in Binhai.
You even got the hotel wrong,
and your drinking capacity is so poor.
I remember I had already checked into the hotel.
Oh my,
I went to the wrong place.
I can't drink that much anymore.
No,
it's this way.
I stood at the door for too long.
The wind makes me dizzy.
Did I do anything embarrassing last night?
If I hadn't picked you up,
you'd still be sleeping on the street.
Who changed my clothes?
Not me.
You came back last night,
and kept asking to take off your clothes.
I asked the cleaner to help you.
Pajamas?
You really tricked me into thinking it was a dog.
I didn't.
Of course I didn't.
You're so conservative.
What time is it?
Huh?
What time is it now?
Half past ten.
Oh no, I'll miss my flight.
Thank you for last night.
I'll treat you to dinner when I get back to Lucheng.
Hello?
[Hello, Mr. Shen.]
[I found something interesting.]
[It's related to Miss Jiang.]
[I've sent it to your phone.]
What painting do you want to buy?
I want to see Ziman.
That's impossible.
Without her permission,
I can't do this.
Help!
Who are you?
Dad.
What do you want?
You still think
your daughter is studying abroad?
What do you mean?
The gambling debts she owes
can't be paid off even if you sell
the whole gallery.
That's impossible.
Ting
doesn't gamble.
Who knows?
Maybe she was taken to Las Vegas by a classmate
and got set up.
It was your doing.
Let's make a deal.
Tell me who is Purple Vine.
I'll pay off
her gambling debts.